ADRIAN WISNIOS

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Diligent university student with over two months of practical work experience. Aiming to leverage the academic knowledge and proven understanding of data collection, manipulation, and visualisation to successfully fill the Data Scientist role at your company.



adrian9.wisnios@gmail.com
Personal Website
0758 7932443
10 Preston Close, CV 8DF Coventry

EXPERIENCE

ABERYSTWYTH UNIVERSITY

Finance Data Analyst, Jun 2021 – Aug 2021

- Collecting, clearing, maintaining, visualising, and analysing stakeholders' data about future projects, grants, capital, and revenue spending.
- Enabling different financial scenarios simulations by priority amendments and automating their influence on the implementation waves and dates.
- Extracting and processing the FTE numbers data from various sources for the benchmarking exercise.
- Preparing Power Bi reports displaying outcomes of the analysis.
- Resolving issues and inconsistencies within the data by contacting stakeholders and university partners.

THE ENGINEERING EDUCATION SCHEME WALES EESW CYMRU

STEM Associate, Feb 2021 – May 2021

- Assisting the students' teams with the project process, providing support with research and beyond.
- Giving guidance and suggestions, maintaining the communication between the teams and the university.
- Attending meetings with EESW staff, Schools and Companies.

EDUCATION

THE UNIVERSITY OF WARWICK

MSc in Statistics, Oct 2021 - Sep 2022

- Relevant Coursework: Data Mining, Statistical Learning and Big Data, Risk Theory, Multivariate Statistics with Advanced Topics, An Introduction to Statistical Practice.
- Extracurricular Activities: Warwick Latin & Ballroom DanceSport club member.

ABERYSTWYTH UNIVERSITY

BSc in Pure Mathematics/Statistics, First Class Honours, Oct 2018 – Jun 2021

- Relevant Coursework: Linear Statistical Models (99%), Stochastic Models in Finance (99%), Applied Statistics (94%), Numerical Solution of Partial Differential Equations (96%), Project in Statistics (86%).
- Awards & Honours: 2021 IMA Graduate Prize (award issued for the best overall performance in mathematical qualification), Pennington Pure Mathematics Memorial Fund, V C Morton Prize in Mathematics, Peter Hancock Scholarship, Collin Easthope Prize in Mathematics, Mathematics Departmental Scholarship, Open Scholarship, Polish Prime Minister Scholarship.

TECH SKILLS

- R
- Python
- PostgrSQL
- MS Excel and Power Bi
- LaTeX

SOFT SKILLS

- Problem-solving and critical thinking.
- Teamwork and communication.
- Resourcefulness and creativity.
- Enthusiasm and willingness to learn.

INTERESTS

- Data Analysis
- Applied Statistics
- Machine Learning Applications
- Dancing and Competitions
- Photography

VOLUNTEERING

ABERYSTWYTH UNIVERSITY STUDENTS' UNION Vice-president and Teaching Coordinator of the DanceSport club, Oct 2019 – Jun 2021

- Preparing students for dancing competitions in Blackpool, Warwick, and Manchester.
- Actively engaging in cultural events such as Arts Festival and Varsity.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Data Scientist with R Track (DataCamp, Jun 2021).
- SQL fundamentals Track (DataCamp, Aug 2021).
- Data Analysis in Excel and Introduction to Power Bi (DataCamp, Jun 2021).
- Institute of Mathematics and its Applications (Associate Membership).

REFERENCES

Dr Jukka Kiukas, Lecturer and Project Supervisor, 01970 622758, jek20@aber.ac.uk Mr David Smith, Procurement Manager, 01970 628611, mks@aber.ac.uk Dr David J Hughes MSc, PhD, CEng, Mentor and Advisor, dhughesny1@gmail.com